So, you've reached an intermediate level of English – congrats!
那么，你已经达到了英语的中级水平——恭喜你！
You can understand most things about familiar topics and can express yourself in most situations.
你能理解大多数熟悉话题的内容，也能在大多数情况下表达自己。
But maybe you've been here a while, and now you're stuck in what we call the 'intermediate plateau'.
但也许你已经在这个阶段停留了一段时间，现在陷入了所谓的"中级平台期"。
Often when we begin learning something, progress is fast and noticeable, but perhaps now it's difficult to see your improvements.
通常，当我们开始学习某件事时，进步是快速而显著的，但现在也许很难看到你的进步。
Let's see if some new ideas can propel your learning forward.
让我们看看是否有一些新想法能够推动你的学习更进一步。
If your study routine mostly consists of flash cards and grammar exercises, it's time to switch it up.
如果你的学习日常主要是抽认卡和语法练习，那么是时候做出改变了。
In an article called 'The four strands' by Paul Nation, he suggests that while such exercises are important for building a strong foundation, we should also make time for more meaning-focused learning.
在保罗·内申的一篇名为《四股力量》的文章中，他建议，虽然这类练习对于打下坚实基础很重要，但我们也应该留出时间进行更注重理解性为主的学习。
That means lots of reading and listening, with a focus on gaining knowledge and enjoyment from the topic itself and learning new vocabulary through context clues.
这意味着大量的阅读和听力，重点是从话题本身获取知识和乐趣，并通过上下文线索学习新词汇。
That way, you immerse yourself in the language and get a feel for how it's used in the real world.
这样，你就能沉浸于语言之中，感受它在现实世界中的使用方式。
But don't stop there!
但别止步于此！
Next, you've got to actually produce the language in a purposeful way.
接下来，你必须以目的为导向真正地产出语言。
According to Merrill Swain's 'Output Hypothesis', speaking helps us to notice holes in our knowledge that we can then work on.
根据梅里尔·斯温的"输出假说"，口语有助于我们注意到知识中的漏洞，然后我们可以加以弥补。
Speaking also gives us the chance to experiment with language and, following feedback, either correct or maintain it.
口语也给了我们试验语言的机会，并根据反馈来纠正或保持它。
What about fluency?
那么流利度呢？
Fluency is using what you already know smoothly and quickly, without focusing on learning new words.
流利度是指流畅而快速地运用已知知识，而不专注于学习新单词。
Set a timer and talk to yourself about a topic, then repeat, setting a shorter timer each time.
计时训练，就某个话题自言自语，然后重复，每次设置更短的时间。
Breaking through the intermediate plateau is tricky.
突破中级平台期是棘手的。
But, the key is not to rely on just one type of activity.
但是，关键在于不要只依赖一种类型的活动。
Experiment with a well-balanced approach, varied materials, and above all, enjoy yourself, and you'll start seeing incremental improvements that'll send you on your way to master English at a higher level.
尝试一种均衡发展的方法，使用多样化的材料，最重要的是，享受学习过程，你就会开始看到渐进的进步，这将引领你达到更高的英语水平。